targetlife.com 2011-09-18

# Privacy Policy | Targetlife

You can find the latest Changes in Our [Privacy Policy Here. Click here to read our Latest privacy policy.](http://iluvdesi.com/topic1889.html)

A copy of this is pasted Bellow. We strongly recommend you to visit above link to see the recent changes. Your entry to this site is governed by your agreement to the terms and conditions we mention in our privacy policy.

> In Case of Any Question Please Mail the Admin @ [](http://targetlife.com/redirect.php?url=http://safemail.justlikeed.net/)  
>  NOTE – Hence Forth the trom “iLuvDesi” means a netowrk of websites which includes domains like  
>  [http://www.targetlife.com](http://www.targetlife.com/) and all the subdomains of targetlife.com, [http://www.getmasti.com](http://www.getmasti.com/) and all its subdomains, [http://www.targetlife.info](http://www.targetlife.info/), and other domains which links to this article after seeking permission from the admin.
> 
> iLuvDesi Forum care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following terms to learn more about our privacy policy. By registering to iLuvDesi-Forums you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.
> 
>   * We will never sell your personal information, or use it for any other purpose other than logging in/out, demographics for our knowledge, and any voluntary feature of the site.
>   * We use cookies with minimal information in them.
>   * We use Google Analytics, which is covered by [Google’s Privacy policy](http://targetlife.com/redirect.php?url=http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html)
>   * We allow you to contact other members via profile pages.
>   * We use Google Adsense and other Advertising Comnpanies placing ads on our site. These third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser’s/computer and they might be using them to track few of your information.
>   * We Absolutely hate popups and we take strong measures to see that you never or seldom face popups. If you find a popup on a page of our network or a link to which we point thru. our website, we beg you to please please please report the link in this topic so that we keep this network clean and safe.
>   * If you are below 13 then you can NOT use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13, Unless you have a written permission from your parents.
> 

> 
> In details
> 
>   1. What does iLuvDesi Privacy Policy Covers?  
>  All the personal information we collect is noted on your profile page. That includes your name, email, date of birth and biographic information. The personal information that you provide is used for Registration purpose. In order for you to participate in iLuvDesi-Forums discussion you must complete a registration form. As part of registration form, we require your email address. 
> 
> Profile Information  
>  iLuvDesi allow other users to browse your full name, IM URL, and few other details within your member profile should you provide this optional information.
> 
>   2. What about Cookies?  
>  Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser in order to check in if you are logged in or out. All the other information is located in iLuvDesi-Forums server. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.  
>  We use Google Adsense and other Advertising Comnpanies placing ads on our site. These third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser’s/computer and they might be using them to track few of our information. Though we make best efforts to maintain your privacy, we are not able to control these third parties cookies. By third parties, we mean Google Adsense, CPX and others. But be rest assured, we try our best to keep your privacy intact and secured, by allowing only those third parties to put cookies on your browser, which are considered safe by us. We accept only those third parties Advertisements on our servers which are Reputed and well known to be safe.
>   3. Membership Validity?  
>  We reserve the right to delete any message, ban any member for any or no reason whatsoever. Members found to be abusing the contact form, using it for commercial purposes, or otherwise breaking the Community Guidelines will have his/her membership suspended.  
>  &nbsp;  
>  Copyright Policy and Disclaimer
> 

> All parts of iLuvDesi.com website and its partners are for private use only. The links and Content posted on this site are not hosted by our servers. So we dont have control over them. We cannot be held responsible for such type of content. You must take any issue related to the content with the repsectd site owner(From which the Content is Linked).
> 
> Also the content is contributed by the community at large. Its difficult for us to control the content posted by the user of iLuvDesi network.  
>  We can only moderate them to a certain level. If you think there is any thing which should not be here, please feel free to contact us on fun4mobiles(at)gmail.com.
> 
> We will be happy to remove the content as we want to keep this community free and clean.  
>  We do not want any unwanted visitor. If you are unsure about whether you are allowed or now, email fun4mobiles(at)gmail.com asking for access before entering.
> 
> Please read our legal policy before you enter the site.
> 
> If you enter this site it means that You agree with our current terms you can not provide any treatment of our hosting ISPs, organization or any persons storing this site information because your actions will be estimated as violation code no. 431.322.12 of the Internet Privacy Act from 1995.
> 
> If you find something objectionable on our site, please put a comment over here with a reason as to why it is objectionable. If we find it suitbale and just, we will remove it from our site. Or Just forward your complaints to fun4mobiles(at)gmail.com ((at) should be replaced by @).
> 
> Also Pleae use softwares provided on the board on your own risk. Please do not blaim us on any problem caused. Reading and downloading any thing from this site means that you automatically agree to this disclaimer even if you have read it or not.
> 
> Children below 13 DO NOT Register  
>  The Federal Trade Commission’s Children Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) require that Web Sites are to obtain parental consent before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from children under 13. If you are below 13 then you cannot use this forum, without getting permissions from your parents. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13
> 
> NEW CHANGES in PRIVACY POLICY
> 
> Google Has started using the DART cookie. This enables GOogle to serve ads based on your visit to sites and other sites on the Internet.
> 
> Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://targetlife.com/redirect.php?url=http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
> 
> To Remind You Once Again  
>  We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies [Click here](http://targetlife.com/redirect.php?url=http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

> One More Change in Policy Privacy
> 
> Please note that Google has started showing 3rd Party Ads in Adsense. This essentially means that 3rd Party ads can appear on all the websites in iLuvDesi.com and Targetlife.com Network.  
>  These third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser’s/computer and they might be using them to track few of our information.
